export const chapter = "Chapter - 11: Prepositions";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What is the primary characteristic of Simple Prepositions?",
          optionA: "They are long phrases",
          optionB: "They consist of one word",
          optionC: "They are compound words",
          correctAnswer: "They consist of one word",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an example of a Compound Preposition?",
          optionA: "under",
          optionB: "behind",
          optionC: "in addition to",
          correctAnswer: "in addition to",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which category do phrases like 'on behalf of' and 'in accordance with' belong to?",
          optionA: "Simple Prepositions",
          optionB: "Compound Prepositions",
          optionC: "Prepositional Phrases",
          correctAnswer: "Prepositional Phrases",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In which situations can a preposition be placed at the end of a sentence?",
          optionA: "Only in affirmative sentences",
          optionB: "Only in negative sentences",
          optionC:
            "Under specific conditions like relative pronouns, interrogative sentences, and passive sentences",
          correctAnswer:
            "Under specific conditions like relative pronouns, interrogative sentences, and passive sentences",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which preposition is typically used with the word 'delight'?",
          optionA: "on",
          optionB: "at",
          optionC: "in",
          correctAnswer: "in",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the correct preposition to use with 'abide'?",
          optionA: "on",
          optionB: "by",
          optionC: "at",
          correctAnswer: "by",
        },
        {
          question: "Which phrase implies searching for something?",
          optionA: "comply with",
          optionB: "aspire after",
          optionC: "take pride in",
          correctAnswer: "aspire after",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'The matter will be enquired into now,' what type of sentence structure is used regarding prepositions?",
          optionA: "Active voice",
          optionB: "Passive voice",
          optionC: "Interrogative",
          correctAnswer: "Passive voice",
        },
        {
          question: "Which preposition is used with the adjective 'similar'?",
          optionA: "to",
          optionB: "with",
          optionC: "of",
          correctAnswer: "to",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What type of combination gives a particular meaning to some nouns, verbs, or adjectives when used with certain prepositions?",
          optionA: "Simile",
          optionB: "Metaphor",
          optionC: "Phrasal Verbs",
          correctAnswer: "Phrasal Verbs",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "Simple Prepositions are made up of ______ word(s).",
          optionA: "two",
          optionB: "one",
          optionC: "three",
          correctAnswer: "one",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Compound Prepositions are formed by joining ______ words together.",
          optionA: "three",
          optionB: "one",
          optionC: "two",
          correctAnswer: "two",
        },
        {
          question: "Prepositional Phrases are composed of ______.",
          optionA: "single prepositions",
          optionB: "phrases and clauses",
          optionC: "groups of words acting as a single preposition",
          correctAnswer: "groups of words acting as a single preposition",
        },
        {
          question: "Generally, a Preposition is placed ______ its Object.",
          optionA: "after",
          optionB: "before",
          optionC: "during",
          correctAnswer: "before",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A Preposition can be put at the end of a sentence when ______.",
          optionA: "expressing surprise",
          optionB: "using an interrogative pronoun",
          optionC: "a relative pronoun is used as the Object of a Preposition",
          correctAnswer:
            "a relative pronoun is used as the Object of a Preposition",
        },
        {
          question: "Words Attached with 'in' include:",
          optionA: "absorbed in, accomplished in, buried in",
          optionB: "aspire in, bark in, charge in",
          optionC: "abstain in, derive in, differentiate in",
          correctAnswer: "absorbed in, accomplished in, buried in",
        },
        {
          question: "Words Attached with 'after' are:",
          optionA: "aspire after, hanker after",
          optionB: "knock after, laugh after",
          optionC: "stare after, mock after",
          correctAnswer: "aspire after, hanker after",
        },
        {
          question: "Prepositions Attached to Words are also known as ______.",
          optionA: "Idioms",
          optionB: "Phrasal Verbs",
          optionC: "Metaphors",
          correctAnswer: "Phrasal Verbs",
        },
        {
          question: "Words Attached with 'over' include:",
          optionA: "crow over, run over",
          optionB: "abide over, charge over",
          optionC: "mock over, stare over",
          correctAnswer: "crow over, run over",
        },
        {
          question: "Words Attached with 'with' comprise:",
          optionA: "acquainted with, afflicted with, agree with",
          optionB: "aspire with, contented with, devoid with",
          optionC: "run with, complain with, responsible with",
          correctAnswer: "acquainted with, afflicted with, agree with",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Simple Prepositions are always composed of more than one word.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Prepositional Phrases can be formed by joining two words together.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Passive sentences, Prepositions are separated from the Verbs.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "A Preposition is always placed after its Object.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Words Attached with 'in' include phrases like 'absorbed in' and 'accomplished in'.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Prepositions Attached to Words are also known as Idioms.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "People with high Musical intelligence excel at group work and maintaining peace in organizations.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Logical-Mathematical intelligence involves number perception and logical problem-solving.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Naturalistic intelligence involves self-awareness and understanding one's own mental-emotional state.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Artificial intelligence has been most successful in achieving Intrapersonal intelligence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
